{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947836997329","data":{"timestamp":" 947836997329"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" 64642a63-ff41-48ed-bb1d-e18adb1bf017"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kusoma kusoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947836998292","data":{"timestamp":" 947836998292"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" 64642a63-ff41-48ed-bb1d-e18adb1bf017"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kusoma kusoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837001191","data":{"timestamp":" 947837001191"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" 64642a63-ff41-48ed-bb1d-e18adb1bf017"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNATAKA"," userResponse":" KUNATAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837001724","data":{"timestamp":" 947837001724"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" 64642a63-ff41-48ed-bb1d-e18adb1bf017"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHO"," userResponse":" MACHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837002367","data":{"timestamp":" 947837002367"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" 64642a63-ff41-48ed-bb1d-e18adb1bf017"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAONE"," userResponse":" YAONE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837006471","data":{"timestamp":" 947837006471"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" 64642a63-ff41-48ed-bb1d-e18adb1bf017"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Masikio yasikie"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASIKIO"," userResponse":" MASIKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837007394","data":{"timestamp":" 947837007394"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" 64642a63-ff41-48ed-bb1d-e18adb1bf017"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Masikio yasikie"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YASIKIE"," userResponse":" YASIKIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837011033","data":{"timestamp":" 947837011033"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" 64642a63-ff41-48ed-bb1d-e18adb1bf017"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837011816","data":{"timestamp":" 947837011816"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" 64642a63-ff41-48ed-bb1d-e18adb1bf017"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOMO"," userResponse":" MDOMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837012789","data":{"timestamp":" 947837012789"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" 64642a63-ff41-48ed-bb1d-e18adb1bf017"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USEME"," userResponse":" USEME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837016634","data":{"timestamp":" 947837016633"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" 64642a63-ff41-48ed-bb1d-e18adb1bf017"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kusoma kusoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837017597","data":{"timestamp":" 947837017597"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" 64642a63-ff41-48ed-bb1d-e18adb1bf017"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kusoma kusoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837020508","data":{"timestamp":" 947837020508"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" 64642a63-ff41-48ed-bb1d-e18adb1bf017"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNATAKA"," userResponse":" KUNATAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837021041","data":{"timestamp":" 947837021041"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" 64642a63-ff41-48ed-bb1d-e18adb1bf017"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHO"," userResponse":" MACHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837021684","data":{"timestamp":" 947837021684"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" 64642a63-ff41-48ed-bb1d-e18adb1bf017"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAONE"," userResponse":" YAONE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837025759","data":{"timestamp":" 947837025759"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" 64642a63-ff41-48ed-bb1d-e18adb1bf017"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Masikio yasikie"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASIKIO"," userResponse":" MASIKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837026682","data":{"timestamp":" 947837026681"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" 64642a63-ff41-48ed-bb1d-e18adb1bf017"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Masikio yasikie"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YASIKIE"," userResponse":" YASIKIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837030300","data":{"timestamp":" 947837030300"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" 64642a63-ff41-48ed-bb1d-e18adb1bf017"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837031083","data":{"timestamp":" 947837031082"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" 64642a63-ff41-48ed-bb1d-e18adb1bf017"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOMO"," userResponse":" MDOMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837032057","data":{"timestamp":" 947837032057"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" 64642a63-ff41-48ed-bb1d-e18adb1bf017"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USEME"," userResponse":" USEME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837035355","data":{"timestamp":" 947837035354"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" 64642a63-ff41-48ed-bb1d-e18adb1bf017"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837035476","data":{"timestamp":" 947837035476"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" 64642a63-ff41-48ed-bb1d-e18adb1bf017"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USEME"," userResponse":" USEME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837046546","data":{"timestamp":" 947837046546"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" e54630e1-81d2-4927-be05-d05cdc5c60a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kusoma kusoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837047521","data":{"timestamp":" 947837047520"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" e54630e1-81d2-4927-be05-d05cdc5c60a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kusoma kusoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837050495","data":{"timestamp":" 947837050495"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" e54630e1-81d2-4927-be05-d05cdc5c60a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNATAKA"," userResponse":" KUNATAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837051037","data":{"timestamp":" 947837051036"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" e54630e1-81d2-4927-be05-d05cdc5c60a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHO"," userResponse":" MACHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837051692","data":{"timestamp":" 947837051691"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" e54630e1-81d2-4927-be05-d05cdc5c60a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAONE"," userResponse":" YAONE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837055823","data":{"timestamp":" 947837055822"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" e54630e1-81d2-4927-be05-d05cdc5c60a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Masikio yasikie"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASIKIO"," userResponse":" MASIKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837056757","data":{"timestamp":" 947837056756"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" e54630e1-81d2-4927-be05-d05cdc5c60a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Masikio yasikie"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YASIKIE"," userResponse":" YASIKIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837060483","data":{"timestamp":" 947837060483"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" e54630e1-81d2-4927-be05-d05cdc5c60a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837061280","data":{"timestamp":" 947837061280"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" e54630e1-81d2-4927-be05-d05cdc5c60a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOMO"," userResponse":" MDOMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837062266","data":{"timestamp":" 947837062265"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" e54630e1-81d2-4927-be05-d05cdc5c60a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USEME"," userResponse":" USEME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837066159","data":{"timestamp":" 947837066159"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" e54630e1-81d2-4927-be05-d05cdc5c60a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kusoma kusoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837067124","data":{"timestamp":" 947837067124"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" e54630e1-81d2-4927-be05-d05cdc5c60a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kusoma kusoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837070029","data":{"timestamp":" 947837070028"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" e54630e1-81d2-4927-be05-d05cdc5c60a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNATAKA"," userResponse":" KUNATAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837070562","data":{"timestamp":" 947837070562"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" e54630e1-81d2-4927-be05-d05cdc5c60a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHO"," userResponse":" MACHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837071207","data":{"timestamp":" 947837071207"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" e54630e1-81d2-4927-be05-d05cdc5c60a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAONE"," userResponse":" YAONE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837075342","data":{"timestamp":" 947837075341"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" e54630e1-81d2-4927-be05-d05cdc5c60a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Masikio yasikie"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASIKIO"," userResponse":" MASIKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837076275","data":{"timestamp":" 947837076275"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" e54630e1-81d2-4927-be05-d05cdc5c60a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Masikio yasikie"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YASIKIE"," userResponse":" YASIKIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837079965","data":{"timestamp":" 947837079964"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" e54630e1-81d2-4927-be05-d05cdc5c60a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837080760","data":{"timestamp":" 947837080759"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" e54630e1-81d2-4927-be05-d05cdc5c60a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOMO"," userResponse":" MDOMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837081745","data":{"timestamp":" 947837081744"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" e54630e1-81d2-4927-be05-d05cdc5c60a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USEME"," userResponse":" USEME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837085065","data":{"timestamp":" 947837085064"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" e54630e1-81d2-4927-be05-d05cdc5c60a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837085153","data":{"timestamp":" 947837085153"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" e54630e1-81d2-4927-be05-d05cdc5c60a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USEME"," userResponse":" USEME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837100578","data":{"timestamp":" 947837100578"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" 957f46e0-5205-4b67-b79d-ad9b495132fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_4+5"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837109976","data":{"timestamp":" 947837109975"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" 957f46e0-5205-4b67-b79d-ad9b495132fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_4+5"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837121139","data":{"timestamp":" 947837121139"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" 957f46e0-5205-4b67-b79d-ad9b495132fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_4+5"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837130382","data":{"timestamp":" 947837130382"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" 957f46e0-5205-4b67-b79d-ad9b495132fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_6+1"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837146445","data":{"timestamp":" 947837146444"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" 957f46e0-5205-4b67-b79d-ad9b495132fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_6+1"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837146708","data":{"timestamp":" 947837146708"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" 957f46e0-5205-4b67-b79d-ad9b495132fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_6+1"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837165794","data":{"timestamp":" 947837165794"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" 957f46e0-5205-4b67-b79d-ad9b495132fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_6+1"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837180368","data":{"timestamp":" 947837180368"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" 957f46e0-5205-4b67-b79d-ad9b495132fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_2+0"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837192643","data":{"timestamp":" 947837192643"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" 957f46e0-5205-4b67-b79d-ad9b495132fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_0+3"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837202592","data":{"timestamp":" 947837202592"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" 957f46e0-5205-4b67-b79d-ad9b495132fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_0+3"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837214353","data":{"timestamp":" 947837214353"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" 957f46e0-5205-4b67-b79d-ad9b495132fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_3+2"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837221752","data":{"timestamp":" 947837221752"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" 957f46e0-5205-4b67-b79d-ad9b495132fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_3+2"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837235142","data":{"timestamp":" 947837235142"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" 957f46e0-5205-4b67-b79d-ad9b495132fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_5+1"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837245419","data":{"timestamp":" 947837245419"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" 957f46e0-5205-4b67-b79d-ad9b495132fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_6+1"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837258750","data":{"timestamp":" 947837258750"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" 957f46e0-5205-4b67-b79d-ad9b495132fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_2+6"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837266689","data":{"timestamp":" 947837266689"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" 957f46e0-5205-4b67-b79d-ad9b495132fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_2+6"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837269664","data":{"timestamp":" 947837269664"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" 957f46e0-5205-4b67-b79d-ad9b495132fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_2+6"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837278217","data":{"timestamp":" 947837278217"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" 957f46e0-5205-4b67-b79d-ad9b495132fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_2+6"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837292119","data":{"timestamp":" 947837292119"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" 957f46e0-5205-4b67-b79d-ad9b495132fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_0+5"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837298798","data":{"timestamp":" 947837298798"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" 957f46e0-5205-4b67-b79d-ad9b495132fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_0+5"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837307579","data":{"timestamp":" 947837307578"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" 37b51ef6-58e2-4f63-a703-678fbb00aa4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837307812","data":{"timestamp":" 947837307812"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" 37b51ef6-58e2-4f63-a703-678fbb00aa4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837308784","data":{"timestamp":" 947837308784"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" 37b51ef6-58e2-4f63-a703-678fbb00aa4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837310069","data":{"timestamp":" 947837310069"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" 37b51ef6-58e2-4f63-a703-678fbb00aa4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837313020","data":{"timestamp":" 947837313019"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" 37b51ef6-58e2-4f63-a703-678fbb00aa4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837313880","data":{"timestamp":" 947837313880"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" 37b51ef6-58e2-4f63-a703-678fbb00aa4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837314204","data":{"timestamp":" 947837314203"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" 37b51ef6-58e2-4f63-a703-678fbb00aa4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837315450","data":{"timestamp":" 947837315450"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" 37b51ef6-58e2-4f63-a703-678fbb00aa4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837319020","data":{"timestamp":" 947837319019"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" 37b51ef6-58e2-4f63-a703-678fbb00aa4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837320003","data":{"timestamp":" 947837320003"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" 37b51ef6-58e2-4f63-a703-678fbb00aa4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837320255","data":{"timestamp":" 947837320255"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" 37b51ef6-58e2-4f63-a703-678fbb00aa4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837321197","data":{"timestamp":" 947837321197"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" 37b51ef6-58e2-4f63-a703-678fbb00aa4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837323509","data":{"timestamp":" 947837323508"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" 37b51ef6-58e2-4f63-a703-678fbb00aa4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837323562","data":{"timestamp":" 947837323562"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" 37b51ef6-58e2-4f63-a703-678fbb00aa4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837336810","data":{"timestamp":" 947837336810"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba ana meno makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBA"," userResponse":" MAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837337613","data":{"timestamp":" 947837337613"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba ana meno makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANA"," userResponse":" MENO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837338364","data":{"timestamp":" 947837338364"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba ana meno makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANA"," userResponse":" ANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837338760","data":{"timestamp":" 947837338760"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba ana meno makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENO"," userResponse":" MENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837341758","data":{"timestamp":" 947837341758"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba ana meno makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKALI"," userResponse":" MAKALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837343571","data":{"timestamp":" 947837343571"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba ana meno makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBA"," userResponse":" MAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837344093","data":{"timestamp":" 947837344093"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba ana meno makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANA"," userResponse":" ANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837344690","data":{"timestamp":" 947837344689"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba ana meno makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENO"," userResponse":" MENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837345546","data":{"timestamp":" 947837345546"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba ana meno makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKALI"," userResponse":" MAKALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837349505","data":{"timestamp":" 947837349505"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba ana meno makali vile vile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837349878","data":{"timestamp":" 947837349878"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba ana meno makali vile vile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANA"," userResponse":" ANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837350278","data":{"timestamp":" 947837350278"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba ana meno makali vile vile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENO"," userResponse":" MENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837351399","data":{"timestamp":" 947837351399"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba ana meno makali vile vile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKALI"," userResponse":" MAKALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837351777","data":{"timestamp":" 947837351777"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba ana meno makali vile vile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837352585","data":{"timestamp":" 947837352584"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba ana meno makali vile vile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837354430","data":{"timestamp":" 947837354429"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba ana meno makali vile vile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837354924","data":{"timestamp":" 947837354923"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba ana meno makali vile vile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANA"," userResponse":" ANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837355463","data":{"timestamp":" 947837355463"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba ana meno makali vile vile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENO"," userResponse":" MENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837356299","data":{"timestamp":" 947837356298"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba ana meno makali vile vile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKALI"," userResponse":" MAKALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837356861","data":{"timestamp":" 947837356860"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba ana meno makali vile vile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837357244","data":{"timestamp":" 947837357243"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba ana meno makali vile vile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837361414","data":{"timestamp":" 947837361414"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAPA"," userResponse":" PAPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837362017","data":{"timestamp":" 947837362016"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANA"," userResponse":" ANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837362527","data":{"timestamp":" 947837362527"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENO"," userResponse":" MENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837363029","data":{"timestamp":" 947837363028"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MAKALI"," userResponse":" START_MAKALI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837364280","data":{"timestamp":" 947837364280"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MAKALI"," userResponse":" MENO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837365991","data":{"timestamp":" 947837365991"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKALI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837367477","data":{"timestamp":" 947837367476"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837369163","data":{"timestamp":" 947837369163"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAPA"," userResponse":" PAPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837369656","data":{"timestamp":" 947837369656"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANA"," userResponse":" ANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837370140","data":{"timestamp":" 947837370139"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENO"," userResponse":" MENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837370778","data":{"timestamp":" 947837370778"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKALI"," userResponse":" MAKALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837371684","data":{"timestamp":" 947837371683"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837374113","data":{"timestamp":" 947837374112"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini baadhi ya wanyama wana meno makali?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837374276","data":{"timestamp":" 947837374276"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini baadhi ya wanyama wana meno makali?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837375197","data":{"timestamp":" 947837375196"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini baadhi ya wanyama wana meno makali?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADHI"," userResponse":" BAADHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837375675","data":{"timestamp":" 947837375674"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini baadhi ya wanyama wana meno makali?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837376681","data":{"timestamp":" 947837376680"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini baadhi ya wanyama wana meno makali?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837377287","data":{"timestamp":" 947837377287"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini baadhi ya wanyama wana meno makali?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANA"," userResponse":" WANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837378335","data":{"timestamp":" 947837378335"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini baadhi ya wanyama wana meno makali?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MENO"," userResponse":" WANA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837379091","data":{"timestamp":" 947837379091"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini baadhi ya wanyama wana meno makali?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENO"," userResponse":" MENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837380919","data":{"timestamp":" 947837380918"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini baadhi ya wanyama wana meno makali?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKALI"," userResponse":" MAKALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837382709","data":{"timestamp":" 947837382708"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini baadhi ya wanyama wana meno makali?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837383285","data":{"timestamp":" 947837383284"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini baadhi ya wanyama wana meno makali?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837383979","data":{"timestamp":" 947837383978"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini baadhi ya wanyama wana meno makali?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADHI"," userResponse":" BAADHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837384163","data":{"timestamp":" 947837384163"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini baadhi ya wanyama wana meno makali?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837384912","data":{"timestamp":" 947837384912"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini baadhi ya wanyama wana meno makali?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837385324","data":{"timestamp":" 947837385323"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini baadhi ya wanyama wana meno makali?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANA"," userResponse":" WANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837385864","data":{"timestamp":" 947837385864"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini baadhi ya wanyama wana meno makali?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENO"," userResponse":" MENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837387082","data":{"timestamp":" 947837387081"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini baadhi ya wanyama wana meno makali?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKALI"," userResponse":" MAKALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837392653","data":{"timestamp":" 947837392653"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe ana meno ya nguvu kwa ajili ya kusaga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NG"," userResponse":" NG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837392655","data":{"timestamp":" 947837392655"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe ana meno ya nguvu kwa ajili ya kusaga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBE"," userResponse":" OMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837393103","data":{"timestamp":" 947837393103"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe ana meno ya nguvu kwa ajili ya kusaga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANA"," userResponse":" ANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837393714","data":{"timestamp":" 947837393713"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe ana meno ya nguvu kwa ajili ya kusaga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENO"," userResponse":" MENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837394395","data":{"timestamp":" 947837394395"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe ana meno ya nguvu kwa ajili ya kusaga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837394398","data":{"timestamp":" 947837394398"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe ana meno ya nguvu kwa ajili ya kusaga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGUVU"," userResponse":" NGUVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837394791","data":{"timestamp":" 947837394790"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe ana meno ya nguvu kwa ajili ya kusaga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837396315","data":{"timestamp":" 947837396314"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe ana meno ya nguvu kwa ajili ya kusaga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AJILI"," userResponse":" AJILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837396683","data":{"timestamp":" 947837396683"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe ana meno ya nguvu kwa ajili ya kusaga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837397119","data":{"timestamp":" 947837397118"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe ana meno ya nguvu kwa ajili ya kusaga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSAGA"," userResponse":" KUSAGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837398963","data":{"timestamp":" 947837398962"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe ana meno ya nguvu kwa ajili ya kusaga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NG"," userResponse":" NG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837398979","data":{"timestamp":" 947837398978"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe ana meno ya nguvu kwa ajili ya kusaga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBE"," userResponse":" OMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837399492","data":{"timestamp":" 947837399492"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe ana meno ya nguvu kwa ajili ya kusaga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANA"," userResponse":" ANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837400152","data":{"timestamp":" 947837400152"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe ana meno ya nguvu kwa ajili ya kusaga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENO"," userResponse":" MENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837400446","data":{"timestamp":" 947837400446"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe ana meno ya nguvu kwa ajili ya kusaga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837401197","data":{"timestamp":" 947837401196"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe ana meno ya nguvu kwa ajili ya kusaga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGUVU"," userResponse":" NGUVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837401539","data":{"timestamp":" 947837401539"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe ana meno ya nguvu kwa ajili ya kusaga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837402368","data":{"timestamp":" 947837402368"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe ana meno ya nguvu kwa ajili ya kusaga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AJILI"," userResponse":" AJILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837402439","data":{"timestamp":" 947837402439"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe ana meno ya nguvu kwa ajili ya kusaga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837403310","data":{"timestamp":" 947837403309"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe ana meno ya nguvu kwa ajili ya kusaga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSAGA"," userResponse":" KUSAGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837407348","data":{"timestamp":" 947837407348"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege hana meno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837408666","data":{"timestamp":" 947837408666"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege hana meno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HANA"," userResponse":" HANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837408756","data":{"timestamp":" 947837408756"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege hana meno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENO"," userResponse":" MENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837410605","data":{"timestamp":" 947837410605"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege hana meno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837411148","data":{"timestamp":" 947837411148"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege hana meno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HANA"," userResponse":" HANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837411851","data":{"timestamp":" 947837411850"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege hana meno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENO"," userResponse":" MENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837413703","data":{"timestamp":" 947837413702"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndege hula namna gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837414406","data":{"timestamp":" 947837414405"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndege hula namna gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837415190","data":{"timestamp":" 947837415189"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndege hula namna gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HULA"," userResponse":" HANA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837417021","data":{"timestamp":" 947837417020"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndege hula namna gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HULA"," userResponse":" HULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837417406","data":{"timestamp":" 947837417405"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndege hula namna gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAMNA"," userResponse":" NAMNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837417943","data":{"timestamp":" 947837417943"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndege hula namna gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" GANI"," userResponse":" HULA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837419112","data":{"timestamp":" 947837419112"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndege hula namna gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" GANI"," userResponse":" NAMNA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837420674","data":{"timestamp":" 947837420673"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndege hula namna gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GANI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837422318","data":{"timestamp":" 947837422317"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndege hula namna gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837423354","data":{"timestamp":" 947837423354"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndege hula namna gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837423859","data":{"timestamp":" 947837423859"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndege hula namna gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HULA"," userResponse":" HULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837424488","data":{"timestamp":" 947837424487"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndege hula namna gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAMNA"," userResponse":" NAMNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837425478","data":{"timestamp":" 947837425477"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndege hula namna gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GANI"," userResponse":" GANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837430211","data":{"timestamp":" 947837430211"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya wana meno ya mbele makubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" PANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837430724","data":{"timestamp":" 947837430724"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya wana meno ya mbele makubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANA"," userResponse":" WANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837431519","data":{"timestamp":" 947837431519"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya wana meno ya mbele makubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENO"," userResponse":" MENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837432023","data":{"timestamp":" 947837432022"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya wana meno ya mbele makubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837432412","data":{"timestamp":" 947837432412"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya wana meno ya mbele makubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBELE"," userResponse":" MBELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837434432","data":{"timestamp":" 947837434432"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya wana meno ya mbele makubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKUBWA"," userResponse":" MAKUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837436182","data":{"timestamp":" 947837436182"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya wana meno ya mbele makubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" PANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837436684","data":{"timestamp":" 947837436683"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya wana meno ya mbele makubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANA"," userResponse":" WANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837437277","data":{"timestamp":" 947837437277"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya wana meno ya mbele makubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENO"," userResponse":" MENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837437500","data":{"timestamp":" 947837437500"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya wana meno ya mbele makubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837438128","data":{"timestamp":" 947837438127"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya wana meno ya mbele makubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBELE"," userResponse":" MBELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837439149","data":{"timestamp":" 947837439148"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya wana meno ya mbele makubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKUBWA"," userResponse":" MAKUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837444430","data":{"timestamp":" 947837444430"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuwa na meno ya mbele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIKUWA"," userResponse":" NILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837444827","data":{"timestamp":" 947837444826"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuwa na meno ya mbele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837445200","data":{"timestamp":" 947837445200"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuwa na meno ya mbele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENO"," userResponse":" MENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837446109","data":{"timestamp":" 947837446108"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuwa na meno ya mbele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837446240","data":{"timestamp":" 947837446240"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuwa na meno ya mbele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBELE"," userResponse":" MBELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837448471","data":{"timestamp":" 947837448470"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuwa na meno ya mbele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIKUWA"," userResponse":" NILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837448784","data":{"timestamp":" 947837448783"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuwa na meno ya mbele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837449317","data":{"timestamp":" 947837449317"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuwa na meno ya mbele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENO"," userResponse":" MENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837449529","data":{"timestamp":" 947837449529"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuwa na meno ya mbele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837450211","data":{"timestamp":" 947837450211"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuwa na meno ya mbele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBELE"," userResponse":" MBELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837454474","data":{"timestamp":" 947837454474"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Meno yangu ya mbele yaling'oka!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENO"," userResponse":" MENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837455581","data":{"timestamp":" 947837455581"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Meno yangu ya mbele yaling'oka!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837455591","data":{"timestamp":" 947837455591"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Meno yangu ya mbele yaling'oka!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837457615","data":{"timestamp":" 947837457614"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Meno yangu ya mbele yaling'oka!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MBELE"," userResponse":" START_MENO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837458886","data":{"timestamp":" 947837458886"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Meno yangu ya mbele yaling'oka!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MBELE"," userResponse":" MENO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837460353","data":{"timestamp":" 947837460352"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Meno yangu ya mbele yaling'oka!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBELE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837463326","data":{"timestamp":" 947837463326"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Meno yangu ya mbele yaling'oka!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YALING"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837464401","data":{"timestamp":" 947837464401"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Meno yangu ya mbele yaling'oka!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" YALING"," userResponse":" MENO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837466028","data":{"timestamp":" 947837466027"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Meno yangu ya mbele yaling'oka!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YALING"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837469010","data":{"timestamp":" 947837469010"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Meno yangu ya mbele yaling'oka!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OKA"," userResponse":" OKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837470733","data":{"timestamp":" 947837470731"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Meno yangu ya mbele yaling'oka!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENO"," userResponse":" MENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837471359","data":{"timestamp":" 947837471358"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Meno yangu ya mbele yaling'oka!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837471482","data":{"timestamp":" 947837471482"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Meno yangu ya mbele yaling'oka!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837471797","data":{"timestamp":" 947837471796"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Meno yangu ya mbele yaling'oka!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBELE"," userResponse":" MBELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837473282","data":{"timestamp":" 947837473282"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Meno yangu ya mbele yaling'oka!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YALING"," userResponse":" YALING"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837473298","data":{"timestamp":" 947837473297"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Meno yangu ya mbele yaling'oka!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OKA"," userResponse":" OKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837476393","data":{"timestamp":" 947837476392"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je una meno mangapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837477617","data":{"timestamp":" 947837477616"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je una meno mangapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNA"," userResponse":" UNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837477695","data":{"timestamp":" 947837477695"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je una meno mangapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENO"," userResponse":" MENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837478715","data":{"timestamp":" 947837478715"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je una meno mangapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANGAPI"," userResponse":" MANGAPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837480380","data":{"timestamp":" 947837480380"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je una meno mangapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837481245","data":{"timestamp":" 947837481245"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je una meno mangapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNA"," userResponse":" UNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837481809","data":{"timestamp":" 947837481808"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je una meno mangapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENO"," userResponse":" MENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837483274","data":{"timestamp":" 947837483273"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je una meno mangapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANGAPI"," userResponse":" MANGAPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837486028","data":{"timestamp":" 947837486027"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Je una meno mangapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837486143","data":{"timestamp":" 947837486143"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" eb8e9b06-12c8-4098-89b9-641b614ec974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je una meno mangapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANGAPI"," userResponse":" MANGAPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837502306","data":{"timestamp":" 947837502305"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" 4c9ad017-af0d-429c-b1dc-356400f566e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_3+0"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837515584","data":{"timestamp":" 947837515584"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" 4c9ad017-af0d-429c-b1dc-356400f566e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_1+2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837528251","data":{"timestamp":" 947837528251"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" 4c9ad017-af0d-429c-b1dc-356400f566e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_1+4"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837541575","data":{"timestamp":" 947837541575"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" 4c9ad017-af0d-429c-b1dc-356400f566e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_2+3"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837547658","data":{"timestamp":" 947837547658"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" 4c9ad017-af0d-429c-b1dc-356400f566e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_2+3"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837550320","data":{"timestamp":" 947837550320"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" 4c9ad017-af0d-429c-b1dc-356400f566e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_2+3"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837561074","data":{"timestamp":" 947837561074"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" 4c9ad017-af0d-429c-b1dc-356400f566e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_2+3"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837575021","data":{"timestamp":" 947837575021"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" 4c9ad017-af0d-429c-b1dc-356400f566e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_4+5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837586157","data":{"timestamp":" 947837586157"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" 4c9ad017-af0d-429c-b1dc-356400f566e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_7+2"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837599165","data":{"timestamp":" 947837599164"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" 4c9ad017-af0d-429c-b1dc-356400f566e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_2+6"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837609290","data":{"timestamp":" 947837609290"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" 4c9ad017-af0d-429c-b1dc-356400f566e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_0+0"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837614983","data":{"timestamp":" 947837614983"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" 4c9ad017-af0d-429c-b1dc-356400f566e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_0+0"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837626832","data":{"timestamp":" 947837626832"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" 4c9ad017-af0d-429c-b1dc-356400f566e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_0+0"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837638620","data":{"timestamp":" 947837638620"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" 4c9ad017-af0d-429c-b1dc-356400f566e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_3+1"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837657929","data":{"timestamp":" 947837657929"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" 4c9ad017-af0d-429c-b1dc-356400f566e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_3+2"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837666661","data":{"timestamp":" 947837666660"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" 4c9ad017-af0d-429c-b1dc-356400f566e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_3+2"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ka.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837676981","data":{"timestamp":" 947837676981"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" 4c9ad017-af0d-429c-b1dc-356400f566e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_3+2"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837681638","data":{"timestamp":" 947837681637"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" 4c9ad017-af0d-429c-b1dc-356400f566e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_3+2"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ka.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837695247","data":{"timestamp":" 947837695247"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" de839d91-6183-4c99-91fc-a5877b80e896"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ka.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kati_kati-saba-kosa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kati"," userResponse":" kati"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ka.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837703837","data":{"timestamp":" 947837703836"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" de839d91-6183-4c99-91fc-a5877b80e896"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ka.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kana_nini-nayo-kana"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kana"," userResponse":" kana"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ka.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837714850","data":{"timestamp":" 947837714850"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" de839d91-6183-4c99-91fc-a5877b80e896"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ka.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kato_nawe-kule-kato"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kato"," userResponse":" kule"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ka.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837725190","data":{"timestamp":" 947837725190"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" de839d91-6183-4c99-91fc-a5877b80e896"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ka.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kato_nawe-kule-kato"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kato"," userResponse":" kato"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ka.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837733697","data":{"timestamp":" 947837733697"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" de839d91-6183-4c99-91fc-a5877b80e896"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ka.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kali_zizi-miti-kali"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kali"," userResponse":" kali"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ka.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837742520","data":{"timestamp":" 947837742520"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" de839d91-6183-4c99-91fc-a5877b80e896"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ka.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kasa_giza-kasa-mvua"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kasa"," userResponse":" kasa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ka.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837752403","data":{"timestamp":" 947837752403"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" de839d91-6183-4c99-91fc-a5877b80e896"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ka.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kali_bila-bali-kali"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kali"," userResponse":" kali"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ka.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837761823","data":{"timestamp":" 947837761822"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" de839d91-6183-4c99-91fc-a5877b80e896"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ka.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kata_kata-kosa-saba"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kata"," userResponse":" kata"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ka.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837774899","data":{"timestamp":" 947837774899"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" de839d91-6183-4c99-91fc-a5877b80e896"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ka.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kato_ziwe-kato-nami"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kato"," userResponse":" ziwe"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ka.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837794810","data":{"timestamp":" 947837794810"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" de839d91-6183-4c99-91fc-a5877b80e896"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ka.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kato_ziwe-kato-nami"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kato"," userResponse":" kato"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ka.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837806612","data":{"timestamp":" 947837806612"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" de839d91-6183-4c99-91fc-a5877b80e896"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ka.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kata_huku-choo-kata"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kata"," userResponse":" huku"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ka.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837815611","data":{"timestamp":" 947837815611"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" de839d91-6183-4c99-91fc-a5877b80e896"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ka.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kata_huku-choo-kata"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kata"," userResponse":" kata"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ka.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837824170","data":{"timestamp":" 947837824170"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" de839d91-6183-4c99-91fc-a5877b80e896"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ka.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kato_tena-kiwe-kato"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kato"," userResponse":" kato"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ka.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837829911","data":{"timestamp":" 947837829910"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" de839d91-6183-4c99-91fc-a5877b80e896"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ka.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_kato_tena-kiwe-kato"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837837257","data":{"timestamp":" 947837837257"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" de839d91-6183-4c99-91fc-a5877b80e896"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ka.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_kato_tena-kiwe-kato"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ka.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837843597","data":{"timestamp":" 947837843597"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" de839d91-6183-4c99-91fc-a5877b80e896"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ka.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_kato_tena-kiwe-kato"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837848705","data":{"timestamp":" 947837848704"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" de839d91-6183-4c99-91fc-a5877b80e896"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ka.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_kato_tena-kiwe-kato"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837855204","data":{"timestamp":" 947837855204"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" de839d91-6183-4c99-91fc-a5877b80e896"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ka.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_kato_tena-kiwe-kato"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:5..15.off1.3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837860495","data":{"timestamp":" 947837860495"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" de839d91-6183-4c99-91fc-a5877b80e896"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ka.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_kato_tena-kiwe-kato"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837867525","data":{"timestamp":" 947837867524"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" de839d91-6183-4c99-91fc-a5877b80e896"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ka.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_kato_tena-kiwe-kato"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837885345","data":{"timestamp":" 947837885345"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" b2223323-41e5-4936-94fa-5bb82a0c9b76"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_c_a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837902042","data":{"timestamp":" 947837902042"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" b2223323-41e5-4936-94fa-5bb82a0c9b76"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837909253","data":{"timestamp":" 947837909253"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" b2223323-41e5-4936-94fa-5bb82a0c9b76"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837921270","data":{"timestamp":" 947837921270"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" b2223323-41e5-4936-94fa-5bb82a0c9b76"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837925473","data":{"timestamp":" 947837925473"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" b2223323-41e5-4936-94fa-5bb82a0c9b76"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837935578","data":{"timestamp":" 947837935577"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" b2223323-41e5-4936-94fa-5bb82a0c9b76"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837940758","data":{"timestamp":" 947837940758"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" b2223323-41e5-4936-94fa-5bb82a0c9b76"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837949267","data":{"timestamp":" 947837949267"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" b2223323-41e5-4936-94fa-5bb82a0c9b76"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837963449","data":{"timestamp":" 947837963449"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" b2223323-41e5-4936-94fa-5bb82a0c9b76"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837968958","data":{"timestamp":" 947837968958"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" b2223323-41e5-4936-94fa-5bb82a0c9b76"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837973058","data":{"timestamp":" 947837973057"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" b2223323-41e5-4936-94fa-5bb82a0c9b76"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837975808","data":{"timestamp":" 947837975808"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" b2223323-41e5-4936-94fa-5bb82a0c9b76"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837978328","data":{"timestamp":" 947837978328"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" b2223323-41e5-4936-94fa-5bb82a0c9b76"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947837987674","data":{"timestamp":" 947837987674"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" b2223323-41e5-4936-94fa-5bb82a0c9b76"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947838000141","data":{"timestamp":" 947838000140"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" b2223323-41e5-4936-94fa-5bb82a0c9b76"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947838010306","data":{"timestamp":" 947838010306"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" b2223323-41e5-4936-94fa-5bb82a0c9b76"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947838013325","data":{"timestamp":" 947838013325"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" b2223323-41e5-4936-94fa-5bb82a0c9b76"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947838024831","data":{"timestamp":" 947838024831"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" b2223323-41e5-4936-94fa-5bb82a0c9b76"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947838027664","data":{"timestamp":" 947838027664"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" b2223323-41e5-4936-94fa-5bb82a0c9b76"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947838037252","data":{"timestamp":" 947838037252"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" b2223323-41e5-4936-94fa-5bb82a0c9b76"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947838038730","data":{"timestamp":" 947838038730"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" b2223323-41e5-4936-94fa-5bb82a0c9b76"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" c"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947838045279","data":{"timestamp":" 947838045279"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" b2223323-41e5-4936-94fa-5bb82a0c9b76"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947838052903","data":{"timestamp":" 947838052903"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" b2223323-41e5-4936-94fa-5bb82a0c9b76"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947838064268","data":{"timestamp":" 947838064267"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" b2223323-41e5-4936-94fa-5bb82a0c9b76"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947838065807","data":{"timestamp":" 947838065807"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" b2223323-41e5-4936-94fa-5bb82a0c9b76"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947838073733","data":{"timestamp":" 947838073733"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" b2223323-41e5-4936-94fa-5bb82a0c9b76"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947838075046","data":{"timestamp":" 947838075046"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" b2223323-41e5-4936-94fa-5bb82a0c9b76"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947838081089","data":{"timestamp":" 947838081089"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" b2223323-41e5-4936-94fa-5bb82a0c9b76"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947838084341","data":{"timestamp":" 947838084341"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" b2223323-41e5-4936-94fa-5bb82a0c9b76"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947838091983","data":{"timestamp":" 947838091983"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" b2223323-41e5-4936-94fa-5bb82a0c9b76"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947838097896","data":{"timestamp":" 947838097896"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" b2223323-41e5-4936-94fa-5bb82a0c9b76"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947838110197","data":{"timestamp":" 947838110197"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" b2223323-41e5-4936-94fa-5bb82a0c9b76"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947838114595","data":{"timestamp":" 947838114595"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" b2223323-41e5-4936-94fa-5bb82a0c9b76"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947838121947","data":{"timestamp":" 947838121947"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" b2223323-41e5-4936-94fa-5bb82a0c9b76"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947838127146","data":{"timestamp":" 947838127146"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" b2223323-41e5-4936-94fa-5bb82a0c9b76"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947838134894","data":{"timestamp":" 947838134894"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" b2223323-41e5-4936-94fa-5bb82a0c9b76"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:5..15.off1.3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947838140261","data":{"timestamp":" 947838140260"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" b2223323-41e5-4936-94fa-5bb82a0c9b76"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947838146753","data":{"timestamp":" 947838146752"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" b2223323-41e5-4936-94fa-5bb82a0c9b76"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947838152251","data":{"timestamp":" 947838152251"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" b2223323-41e5-4936-94fa-5bb82a0c9b76"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ki.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947838157960","data":{"timestamp":" 947838157959"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" b2223323-41e5-4936-94fa-5bb82a0c9b76"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:5..15.off1.3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947838162723","data":{"timestamp":" 947838162722"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" b2223323-41e5-4936-94fa-5bb82a0c9b76"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ki.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947838167751","data":{"timestamp":" 947838167751"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" b2223323-41e5-4936-94fa-5bb82a0c9b76"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ki.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947838176570","data":{"timestamp":" 947838176569"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" b2223323-41e5-4936-94fa-5bb82a0c9b76"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947838181695","data":{"timestamp":" 947838181694"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" b2223323-41e5-4936-94fa-5bb82a0c9b76"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947838199357","data":{"timestamp":" 947838199357"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" b2223323-41e5-4936-94fa-5bb82a0c9b76"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:5..15.off1.3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947838208872","data":{"timestamp":" 947838208872"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" b2223323-41e5-4936-94fa-5bb82a0c9b76"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.ki.rand.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947838216311","data":{"timestamp":" 947838216310"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" b2223323-41e5-4936-94fa-5bb82a0c9b76"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947838221701","data":{"timestamp":" 947838221701"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" b2223323-41e5-4936-94fa-5bb82a0c9b76"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.ki.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947838227958","data":{"timestamp":" 947838227958"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" b2223323-41e5-4936-94fa-5bb82a0c9b76"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:5..15.off1.3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947838233950","data":{"timestamp":" 947838233949"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" b2223323-41e5-4936-94fa-5bb82a0c9b76"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::begin.wrd.ku.rand.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947838239025","data":{"timestamp":" 947838239024"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" b2223323-41e5-4936-94fa-5bb82a0c9b76"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947838244391","data":{"timestamp":" 947838244390"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" b2223323-41e5-4936-94fa-5bb82a0c9b76"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.ku.rand.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947838250631","data":{"timestamp":" 947838250630"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" b2223323-41e5-4936-94fa-5bb82a0c9b76"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:5..15.off1.3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947838256663","data":{"timestamp":" 947838256662"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" b2223323-41e5-4936-94fa-5bb82a0c9b76"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.ku.show.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947838264232","data":{"timestamp":" 947838264232"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" b2223323-41e5-4936-94fa-5bb82a0c9b76"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947838269964","data":{"timestamp":" 947838269964"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" b2223323-41e5-4936-94fa-5bb82a0c9b76"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ku.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947838277601","data":{"timestamp":" 947838277601"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" b2223323-41e5-4936-94fa-5bb82a0c9b76"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:2..12.off1.2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947838283852","data":{"timestamp":" 947838283852"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" b2223323-41e5-4936-94fa-5bb82a0c9b76"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.ku.show.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947838290229","data":{"timestamp":" 947838290229"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" b2223323-41e5-4936-94fa-5bb82a0c9b76"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947838299836","data":{"timestamp":" 947838299836"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" b2223323-41e5-4936-94fa-5bb82a0c9b76"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.ku.rand.38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947838315965","data":{"timestamp":" 947838315964"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" b2223323-41e5-4936-94fa-5bb82a0c9b76"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947838339410","data":{"timestamp":" 947838339410"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" b2223323-41e5-4936-94fa-5bb82a0c9b76"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::begin.wrd.na.rand.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947838344645","data":{"timestamp":" 947838344645"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" b2223323-41e5-4936-94fa-5bb82a0c9b76"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947838350209","data":{"timestamp":" 947838350209"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" b2223323-41e5-4936-94fa-5bb82a0c9b76"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947838362025","data":{"timestamp":" 947838362025"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_110257"," gameId":" b2223323-41e5-4936-94fa-5bb82a0c9b76"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}